[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country did the Goulash soup originally come from?", "correct_answer": "Hungary", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "India", "Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the name of the Suea Rong Hai dish that is popular in Thailand?", "correct_answer": "Crying tiger", "incorrect_answers": ["Spiders web", "Angry octopus", "Mothers heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital city of Switzerland?", "correct_answer": "Bern", "incorrect_answers": ["Bonn", "Berlin", "Zurich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the water-fearing sheriff and his family in the 1975 thriller Jaws?", "correct_answer": "Brody", "incorrect_answers": ["Brandford", "Brophy", "Bradley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Potatoes are being called various names around the globe. Which of these names refers to potatoes?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Tatoes", "Praties", "Taters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Denzel Washington turned down both the roles of Detective David Mills in Se7en and Cinque in Amistad.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lactic acid bacteria help achieve this.", "correct_answer": "Keep vegetables fresher", "incorrect_answers": ["Preserve pollen aroma", "Prevent milk from turning into yogurt", "Keep honey diluted in water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie High Noon, Amy Fowler Kane heard rumors about Wills possible dalliances with a local woman. Which actress played this woman?", "correct_answer": "Katy Jurado", "incorrect_answers": ["Virginia Mayo", "Eve Arden", "Susan Hayward"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to a theory, palm readers should explore only the left hand of people which of the following people?", "correct_answer": "Women", "incorrect_answers": ["Unmarried people", "Men", "Children"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Aunt Sally leave to Paulina after her death in The Fighting Temptations 2003 movie?", "correct_answer": "A collection of church hats", "incorrect_answers": ["$10,000", "Her plus-size dresses and skirts", "The church choir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the term that denotes an airplane accident in which the plane is a total loss?", "correct_answer": "Hull loss incident", "incorrect_answers": ["Burial incident", "Decommission accident", "Finishing accident"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which cartoon dog is one of Mickey Mouses best friends?", "correct_answer": "Goofy", "incorrect_answers": ["Happy", "Minnie", "Doggie"]}]